savers.pk 2017-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Savers.pk is a Part of  **25th Hour Pvt. Ltd**. We highly admire your privacy and like to protect customer private information. When you register initially on our site, we gather details from you when you place your order. You also are subscribed to our promotional offers that we offer occasionally. We have set some basic yet the most essential privacy policy, so to keep our consumer’s confidential information highly protected.

**What information do we collect?  **

At Savers.pk, we gather information from you when you register initial time, place an order, subscribe to our promotional offers or fill out a form. 

When ordering or registering on our site, you may be asked to provide basic details such as name, e-mail address, mailing address and phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, make use of cookies to serve ads on your sites. User may opt out of the use of the cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

**What do we use your information?  **

Any of the information we accumulate from you may be used for one of the following reasons: 

**\- To personalize your online experience  **

  (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual requests)

**\- To improve our website  time to time**

  (We constantly strive to progress our website based on the information and feedback we obtain from consumers)

**\- To improve customer service  **

  (Your information supports us to more effectively respond to your buyer service requests and support needs)

**\- To process transactions easily**

  Your information, whether public or private, will not be shared, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other business for any reason whatsoever,   without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested!

**\- To send periodic emails  **

  The email address that customer provides for order processing, will only be used to send you info and updates relating to your order.

**How do we protect your information?  **

Savers.pk implements a variety of security methods, so to maintain the safety of consumer’s personal information when they enter, submit, or access their personal details.  

We make use of a secure server. All given sensitive/credit card information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Database to be only retrieved by those authorized with distinctive access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information trustworthy.  

After making transaction, your private information (credit cards, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers any longer.

**Do we use cookies?  ** 

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that allows the service providers systems to distinguish your browser and capture and remember certain details.  

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, recognize and save your preferences for upcoming visits and accumulate aggregate data about site traffic and site communication so that we can offer improved site experiences and tools in the future.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  **

We do share, trade, or transfer any customer’s confidential information to outside parties. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or safeguard others or ours rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or promotional uses.

**Online Privacy Policy Only  **

This online privacy policy applies only to information gathered through our website and not to information that is collected offline.

**Your Consent  ** 

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy  ** 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us  ** 

If there are any questions regarding our privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.  

Pakistan

You can also send us your email at:
